<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>HeinrichHartmann.com</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on HeinrichHartmann.com</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Blog Reboot</title>
      <link>/posts/blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/blog/</guid>
      <description>This blog has gotten a new look, recently. For the last ~5 years this blog has been build with Jekyll, now it has been migrated to Hugo. With this migration I implemented a few changes, that were longer in the making.
Articles as stand-alone HTML pages Anticipating future migrations of the content, we treat posts as documents that should be as stand-alone as possible. This means:
  No header/footer content, just a link to the Home at the top.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>Credits  Social icons by Alfredo Creates jekyll theme by Tom Preston-Werner  Impressum This statment of ownership is legally mandated in Germany (cf. Wikipedia).
Impressum dieser Website erstellt über den Generator der Deutschen Anwaltshotline AG
Angaben gem. § 5 TMG
Betreiber und Kontakt:
Dr. Heinrich Hartmann Am Bökel 3 32351 Stemwede Telefonnummer: +49 1525 3638134 E-Mail-Adresse: heinrich@heinrichhartmann.com USt-IdNr.: DE295519544  Die Europäische Kommission stellt eine Plattform zur Online-Streitbeilegung (OS) bereit, die Sie hier finden.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Better Crash Reporting</title>
      <link>/posts/crash/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/crash/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Crash events are some of the more serious events that can happen when operating a service.  Usually
it is crashing components that cause cascading failures and service outages.  It is critical to have
good visibility into those events, since they can cause major damage and should be avoided.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
